# MARIE MOORE

#### FRONT DEVELOPER E N D W E B REACT JAVASCRIPT

### CONTACT



07-49-66-88-83



marie.rodiet@gmail.com



77163 MORTCERF



ttps://marierodiet.github.io /portfolio/

### HARD SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SASS
- JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- REACT, REDUX
- FIGMA, WIREFRAME
- GIT
- TESTING, DEBUGGING
- RESPONSIVE APPS

### LANGUAGES

English



French



Chinese



### SOFT SKILLS

- Time Management
- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Critical Thinking
- Adaptability

### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am actively looking for a position as a front end web developer in a company that will challenge me and bring me to the next level.

I am a self-motivated professional with a strong capacity for finding solutions, something I have learned through more than a decade of international life, first in China, then in the United States. The drive that led me to gain functional or native fluency in Chinese and English has also let me to pursue coding languages with the same passion. Put simply: I love communication and problem-solving in all its forms, whether that means with other people, or as a bridge between people and their technology. I am looking for a work environment that will challenge me in both



### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor in React JS Front-End Web Developement

OPENCLASSROOMS (2021- November 2022)

### Responsive Web Design

# JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

FREECODECAMP CERTIFICATIONS(2021-2022)

### M.A French Literature

University of Oregon (2014-2016)

### Bachelor English History and Literature

Université du Littoral Côte d'Opale (2007-2009)

University of Malta (2009-2010)



### WORK EXPERIENCE

### French Language Instructor, Eugene OR 2014-2016

I taught beginning and intermediate French to university undergraduates. I learned to become a motivator in language acquisition because so many of my students were taking French as a required course, rather than by choice. Sparking interest in my students made my work enjoyable and effective. I planned, prepared, and delivered lessons on all aspects of spoken and written French. I also provided feedback and found ways to relate to students from a variety of different cultural backgrounds.

# Administrative Support Specialist, Lane Community College, Eugene OR 2017-2020

I provided administrative and translation support in French and Chinese for staff of the International Student Program.

# MARIE MOORE

#### DÉVELOPPEUSE F R O N T E N D W E B J A V A S C R I P T REACT

### CONTACT



07-49-66-88-83



marie.rodiet@gmail.com



77163 MORTCERF



ttps://marierodiet.github.io /portfolio/

### HARD SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SASS
- JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- REACT, REDUX
- FIGMA, WIREFRAME
- GIT
- TESTING, DEBUGGING
- RESPONSIVE APPS

### LANGAGES

Anglais



Français



Chinois



### SOFT SKILLS

- Organisée
- Esprit pratique
- A l'écoute
- Sens critique
- Adaptabilité

### PROFIL PROFESSIONEL

Je recherche activement un emploi en tant que développeur web front end au sein d'une équipe qui saura mettre à profit mes compétences et les enrichir.

Je suis une personne appliquée et enthousiaste disposant d'une forte capacité à résoudre les problèmes que je rencontre. Je dois mon pouvoir d'adaptation et d'esprit pratique à une décennie de vie internationale, tout d'abord en Chine puis aux Etats-Unis. Le désir qui m'a conduit à devenir trilingue est le même que celui qui m'a conduit à maîtriser les langages de programmation: la communication et la résolution de problèmes sous toutes leurs formes sont mes passions; que ce soit avec les autres ou en tant que pont entre les gens et leurs outils technologiques. Je recherche un environnement de travail qui m'apportera un défi quotidien dans ces deux domaines.

### ÉDUCATION

## Niveau VI Web Développement Front-End JS React

OPENCLASSROOMS (2021- Novembre 2022)

### Responsive Web Design

# JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

CERTIFICATS FREECODECAMP (2021-2022)

### Master Littérature Française

University of Oregon (2014-2016)

### Licence d'Anglais LCE, Option Chinois

Université du Littoral Côte d'Opale (2007-2009)

University of Malta (2009-2010)

# EXPÉRIENCE PROFESSIONELLE

### French Language Instructor, Eugene OR 2014-2016

J'ai enseigné le Français débutant et intermédiaire aux étudiants de Licence. Puisque le Français leur était imposé par leur cursus universitaire, j'ai appris à éveiller leur curiosité culturelle et linguistique. Susciter leur intérêt à rendu mon travail à la fois agréable et efficace. Je planifiais, préparais et enseignais mes leçons en incluant tous les aspects de la langue parlée, écrite et en tant qu'expression culturelle.

# Administrative Support Specialist, Lane Community College, Eugene OR 2017-2020

Je faisais partie de l'équipe administrative pluridisciplinaire au sein du Programme des Etudiants Internationaux, en particulier auprès des étudiants Africains Francophones et Chinois.